Yui, are you still in bed?
Are you feeling okay?
Want to stay home again?
Hey, Yaegashi!
Finally decided to grace
us with your presence?
Yeah, something came up.
You missed out big time
since you didn't get to see
your darling's big scene.
Yeah, that was brilliant.
My darling?
The girl in your club.
You mean Nagase?
Oh, so you've got your
sights set on Nagase.
Wh-Why would you say that?!
You, Inaba, and Nagase are
the only StuCS members in our class.
And when I mentioned your darling,
you immediately brought up Nagase.
You tricked me!
Watase!
The soccer team's supposed to assemble
in the locker room for a meeting.
Ugh, it's lunch time.
Well, you know where to find me
if you need relationship advice.
You can always rely on me. Bye!
H-Hey!
Big scene?
Taichi,
why were you late?
Did something happen?
Yeah.
I probably had a desire unleashed—
Other people can hear us, fool!
Can you try to reprimand me
in a less painful fashion?
There won't be any pain if you
don't do anything stupid.
I've never used violence
without just cause.
What? Really?
Huh?
Never mind.
So what desire was unleashed?
I'm guessing it was...
...my desire to sleep.
Huh?
What?
Ow!
Don't scare me like that
over just wanting to sleep.
It was pretty serious!
Well, I was asleep, so I
don't remember any of it.
Big brother, wake up or you'll be late.
Wake up already!
Big brother? Big brother!
Big brother!
Wake up, big brother!
My mom had to calm my sister down
before she would go to school.
I heard everything from
my mom when I woke up.
They didn't call the hospital?
If I hadn't woken up, they would
have called an ambulance.
I'll need to apologize to my sister.
I sent her an e-mail,
but I should get her something...
Shut up, sister lover!
It's only natural for a
brother to love his sister!
If she couldn't wake you up,
your desire must have been unleashed.
While you were asleep,
there was an episode,
and your desire to sleep a little
longer was unleashed, I guess.
So, I've been wondering.
Was Nagase's desire to
sleep also unleashed?
Taichi wants an answer.
Say, Taichi...
Have you ever had the urge to break
the tension when everyone's
acting really serious?
Not really.
Don't tell me...
There was a quiz this morning,
so everyone was on edge.
And suddenly I had an urge to shout...
Yahoo!
Yahoo...
I managed to convince everyone that I
was half asleep at the time.
The class thought it was hilarious.
Plus, they seemed to write it
off as Iori being herself.
That was the worst part!
If everyone thinks I'm being myself
when I suddenly shout "Yahoo!" in the
middle of class, what does that say?!
That you're the kind of
person who likes to shout
"Yahoo!" in the middle of class?
Don't join them!
Anyway, you guys have
some tame desires.
Yui didn't come to school?
I told her about Heartseed.
I mentioned that the five of
us needed to talk together.
I called Yui earlier and
said we might drop by.
Don't bother.
I'll be back at school
by the end of the week.
By then, everybody will have gotten over
what happened yesterday.
Yui...
Damn...
Heartseed's messing
everything up again.
If he makes Yui cry again,
I'll make him pay!
Aoki!
Name five good things about Kiriyama Yui!
Cute! Cheerful! Strong! Super cute!
Pretty hair! Small! Innocent!
Childish in a good way.
Wait, I need more than five!
You shouldn't have used
"cute" twice, then.
So, did that help you calm down?
Huh?
Avoid intense emotional outbursts.
It won't matter if your
desires are unleashed
if you don't have any meaningful desires.
You're right.
But I can't help it.
Yeah, if all it makes you
do is shout "Yahoo!"
then we can all laugh it off.
Wait, Taichi.
Is this a new form of bullying?
Are you bullying me?
So when I get irritated or angry,
I should think about Yui and calm down.
Yeah, that works in your case.
Still, I'm worried about Yui.
She's probably still in shock
after beating up those guys.
I have to help her!
I have to go.
Wait, Taichi?
Not good! His desire was unleashed!
Wait, Taichi!
Wait! Wait!
Get a hold of yourself, Taichi!
I have to go help her!
I have to go help Kiriyama!
You really like to help people, huh?
It's kinda creepy.
Let me go! Let me go!
Wake up, Taichi!
Calm down!
Okay, Iori! Throw yourself on Taichi!
Roger that!
Wait, why me?!
Aoki's stronger!
No, we might be able to change things up
or stop this episode if we override
his current desire with a stronger one.
Are you sure that will work?
It's worth a shot.
Make like you're crawling up his body
to awaken his perverted side!
Wait, wait.
Well, I don't really mind...
Iori-chan, do it for Taichi's sake!
Hey, stop fooling around!
Got a problem?
It would have been
dangerous to let you go.
This selfless freak always worries
more about other people.
Wait, did he calm down?
Huh?
Oh, yeah...
I guess our desires aren't
unleashed for that long.
Nothing will happen if it's something
that can't be done right away.
But generally, spur-of-the-moment desires
are driven by your current
circumstances, right?
Your mind tends to focus
on your surroundings.
Aoki made a valid point!
Why are you so surprised?!
I have my moments!
What's Heartseed up to this time?
It's the same as when we
were swapping bodies.
He wants to watch us and be entertained.
This phenomenon just
serves as a catalyst.
Don't ogle me.
I wasn't ogling you!
Wait, do I look like I'm
ogling people by default?
I'd say that you're in the
most danger this time around.
Huh? What do you mean?
Well, you were willing to die for Iori
when you were sober.
What if that desire is unleashed?
You might
actually die this time around.
I checked Class 1, but
Yui was absent again.
She said she was okay when
I called her yesterday.
I'm hoping that she didn't break.
What do you mean by that?
Just like last time,
any one of us could break at any moment.
We need to go to Yui's house today.
Yeah.
Drop the long faces.
If you show up looking so grim,
Yui might end up feeling worse.
Yes?
Kiriyama-san, let's play!
Huh? Wait, Iori?
No way, why?
And I'm here, too!
Along with Inaba-chan and Taichi!
There aren't any cameras.
Everybody's here?
Yeah, all of the StuCS members are here.
We came to see you.
Can we come inside?
Is someone else there right now?
No one else is home.
But you can't come in. Leave.
You don't want any boys inside?
Is it okay if only
Inaban and I come in?
That's not it.
Just...
Oh.
Are you Yui's friends?
Come on, Yui. Open the door.
Your friends are here.
Tell them to leave.
I'm sorry.
She's locked herself in her
room and refuses to come out.
It's okay, ma'am.
She's just a little upset right now.
I'm sure she'll cheer up soon.
Yes, "Mom"!
Let us handle this!
Thank you for being so
good to my daughter.
It's nothing.
Let me know if you need anything.
Yui, you shouldn't make your Mom sad.
Anyway, can we talk for a bit?
We've got big trouble.
Leave.
I appreciate your concern.
I'll be back at school soon.
This is a pain.
Are you going to do something?
No, I'm just going to say the
magic words to make the door open.
What are you, exactly?
Okay, then.
I'm going to reveal Kiriyama
Yui-san's secrets now.
First, her BWH is an A—
Stop! Stop! Stop!
I'll let you in, so stop!
It would have been more fun
if I got to say more stuff.
You're too scary, Inaban.
Sorry about dropping in without warning.
But...
No, it's okay.
I should be the one to apologize.
Are you feeling sick or something?
We can go if you are.
Wait, there's a big zit
on your forehead...
Wait! Wait! Wait!
Don't look! I made a huge mistake!
Did you go on a binge?
Th-That's not it!
Yesterday, I suddenly had the urge
to gorge myself on sweets.
I wanted to die when I started
counting all the calories.
Wow, that's terrifying.
You must have had an episode
while you were hungry.
You wouldn't have stayed home from
school because of that zit?
Even I'm not that stupid!
Then it's because Heartseed's
been unleashing your desires?
That's silly.
We're all in the same boat.
But...
I don't want to hurt anyone else.
When I saw those girls surrounded
by a bunch of guys,
I really wanted to help them.
Then I went berserk.
That was because Heartseed
did something funny to you.
But I was the one who wanted
to hurt them badly
since I have a strong aversion to men.
Who knows what might happen next time?
I can't go outside like this!
Stop playing the victim.
Inaban?
You don't get to be the only
one who hides in her room.
Well, if I don't run into
anyone, I can't hurt them.
Do you understand the current situation?
You must not.
Hey, Inaba...
Nothing can go wrong if you
stay away from everyone else.
Sure, I considered trying that.
But the problem is that Heartseed
might not be amused.
He's looking for entertainment.
And he'll take steps
to be entertained if necessary.
Like having one of us
jump in the river,
or something even worse!
All five of us may be put in danger!
Do you realize how much worse
it is for everyone else if you bail?!
Well?!
I don't know...
What should I do?
Take some responsibility!
Don't expect someone else
to help you out if you cry!
Inaban!
Sorry, Yui.
I didn't mean to be so hard on you.
I must have had an episode.
But that's how you really feel.
How would I know?!
Don't ask me!
What?
I just wanted to know
what was going on
with that Kiriyama girl.
That's what I want to know!
What are you snapping at me for?
Oh, um...
No.
Well, I didn't mean to yell at—
You think you're better because
you have a cute face?
I don't.
Hey, shouldn't you help out?
Stop, that's enough.
Huh?
Sorry, Setouchi-san.
Kiriyama-san's absence is
sort of a sensitive issue.
She lashed out at you because
everyone keeps asking
her the same question.
Isn't that right, Nagase-san?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
I'm worried about her too, so I just...
I'm sorry. It was all my fault.
You don't have to be so formal.
And I kind of embarrassed
myself at the end.
I'm also sorry.
Fujishima-san is so awesome.
Inaba...
I'm going home.
Huh?
Bye.
Wait, Inaba.
Why are you leaving?
Do you have something to do?
Not really.
Not really?
Kiriyama was absent again.
So?
We need to go see her again today.
My presence would be detrimental.
Is that why you stayed out of it
when Nagase got in a fight?
I can't afford to do anything
that makes the situation worse.
So I won't be going to the club room.
But Kiriyama's hurting right now.
Sure, I understand that
yesterday was hard on you...
That's no excuse.
How can you just give up?!
We have to do something!
Not everyone puts other people
before themselves the way you do.
There are times when I'm too
busy with my own problems.
That doesn't make it okay
to ignore someone who's suffering!
You can't force other people to
follow your sickening ideals!
I'm disappointed, Inaba.
I never thought you would
give up on your friends.
I thought you were better than that.
I guess I'm not good enough for you.
Inaban, Taichi, and me...
we all have the worst timing.
I've been trying to call Inaba,
but she won't answer.
I'll apologize when I see
her tomorrow morning.
Yup, the best response would
be to apologize and move on.
Inaba-chan knows that you meant no harm.
Okay, it'll just be the three
of us visiting Yui today.
Yup, Yui should be feeling better now.
I told you guys to cut it out!
Today, I'm doing things my way.
You're just a selfish freak
who doesn't want to see Yui look sad!
It's getting lonely.
Well, you were right.
I've always thought that humans
are supposed to hurt each other.